[Music]
tell me that I'm special
tell me I look
pretty tell me I'm a little angel sweet
of your
city say what I'm
dying cuz I'm dying to hear you tell me
I'm that new thing tell me that I'm
relevant tell me that I got a big heart
and back it up with evidence
I need it and I don't know
why this sat night isn't it
lonely I do anything to make you want me
give it up if you told me that I be the
number one girl in your eyes you're one
and only so what's it going to take for you
to want me
i' give it all up if you told me that i'
be the number one girl girl in your
eyes tell me I'm going real big places
down to earth so friendly and even
through all the phases tell me you
extend
me well that's all I'm dying to here
yeah I'm dying to hear you tell me that
you need me tell me that I'm L tell me
that I'm worth it that I'm
enough I need it and I don't know
why this and night isn't it
lonely do anything to make you want me
give it all up if you told me that I'll
be the number one girl in your eyes
you're want
know so what's it going to take for you
want me give it up if you told me that I
be the number one girl in your eyes the
girl in your
eyes the girl in your
eyes tell me I'm the number one girl I'm
the number one curl in your
eyes Cur in your
eyes tell me I'm the number one girl I'm
the number one color in your
eyes isn't it
onlyon to anything make you want me I
give it all up if you you told me that
I'd be the number one girl in your eyes
go on
know so what's it come take for you want
me give it up if you told me that I be
the I'm I Girl In Your
Eyes the number one girl in your eyes is
you're want